http://www.healthstatus.com/privacy-data-policy/

Get Healthy
Ultimate Transformation
Purium Products
CoupleWise – A Relationship Program Designed for Every Relationship
Ovulation
more….
Privacy and Data PolicyPrivacy and Data Policy
Privacy:::
HealthStatus.com is committed to safeguarding consumer privacy on our Web site. We operate under the following set of strict privacy principles: The only information HealthStatus.com obtains about individual visitors to its Web site is that supplied voluntarily by visitors. In cases when HealthStatus.com may need personal information to provide visitors with customized content or to inform them about new features or services, visitors are explicitly asked for that information. Personally identifiable information provided by visitors (name, e-mail or home address, etc.) will not be disclosed to anyone unless visitors indicate that HealthStatus.com may do so. Only statistical information about our visitors as a group (usage habits, demographics) may be shared with any partner of HealthStatus.com. Personally identifiable information will not be shared at any time without the visitor’s permission. HealthStatus.com employs strict security measures to safeguard online transactions; personal information is stored in a secured database and always sent via an encrypted Internet channel.
User Content:::
Please note that whenever you publicly disclose information about yourself online (e.g., through email, social networking platforms, forums, message boards, chat areas, comment areas, or similar web pages), such information may be collected, exported and used by people that you do not know. Posting personal information in public places may result in unsolicited communications, including unwanted email messages or other forms of contact. Always be smart about the information you provide online.  We bear no responsibility for any action or policies of any third parties who collect any information you may disclose on the Company Site.
Security:::
The HealthStatus.com Web site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. HealthStatus.com employs strict security measures to safeguard online transactions; personal information is stored in a secured and encrypted database.
IP Address:::
Upon visiting the Company Site, we may collect and store your browser type and IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer the Company Site, to help identify and analyze user trends, to customize content and advertisements offered to you, and to gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.
Cookies:::
Our site places a text file called a “cookie” in the browser files of your computer. Cookies are pieces of information that a Web site transfers to an individual’s hard disk for record keeping purposes. Our site uses cookies during your online session to aid in security and authorization. They do enable HealthStatus.com to relate your use of the site to information that you have specifically and knowingly provided to our site.
Registration:::
Our site’s registration system requires users to give us contact information such as their name and e-mail address, additionally optional demographic information such as a ZIP code, sex, age or country will be collected. The customer’s contact information is used to contact the visitor when necessary. Upon registration users choose (opt-in) to receive future mailings; see the choice/opt-in section below. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor the visitor’s experience at our site, showing the visitor content that reflects their stated preferences. This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis, but it does not indicate the identity of individual users.
External Links:::
In order to provide visitors with greater value, HealthStatus.com may provide links to various third party Web sites. However, even if a third-party affiliation exists between HealthStatus.com and that destination site, HealthStatus.com exercises no authority over linked sites, each of which maintains independent privacy and data collection policies and procedures. HealthStatus.com assumes no responsibility or liability for these independent methods or actions and is not responsible for the independent policies or procedures of destination sites. Similarly, HealthStatus.com cannot take responsibility for the privacy initiatives or the content of such Web sites. These destination links are provided only for your convenience, and as such, you access them at your own risk. However, HealthStatus.com wishes to ensure the integrity of the HealthStatus.com Web site and its destination links, so any comments pertaining to the HealthStatus.com Web site or any sites accessed through HealthStatus.com links are greatly appreciated.
Advertising:::
This website does use third-party advertising Companies and affiliate programs as a means of generating an income. Be advised that these companies may use information in respect to your visits to this site as a means of providing information about goods and services that may be of interest to you. They will not utilize information such as name,address,email address or telephone information that you provide through opt in means on this site. Google as an add provider to this site uses cookies to serve ads to the site. This is the DART cookie and visitors may opt out of the DART cookie system by visiting https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ads/
Contests:::
We run contests on our site in which we ask visitors for contact and demographic information. The customer’s contact information is used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may choose to receive future mailings; see the choice/opt-in section below. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis, but it does not indicate the identity of individual users.
Choice/Opt-In:::
Our site gives users the opportunity to opt-in to receive communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor. This site also gives users the following options for removing their information from our database in order to stop receiving communications or our service. You can send e-mail to privacy@HealthStatus.com You can send mail to the following postal address: Privacy Department HealthStatus LLC, 9801 Fall Creek Road Box 112, Indianapolis, IN 46256 You can call the following telephone number: 317.823.2687
Correct/Update:::
To change or modify information previously provided: e-mail privacy@HealthStatus.com
About Latest Posts Follow usHealthStatusHealthStatus has been operating since 1998 providing the best interactive health tools on the Internet, millions of visitors have used our health risk assessment, body fat and calories burned calculators.The HealthStatus editorial team has continued that commitment to excellence by providing our visitors with easy to understand high quality health content for many years.
Follow usLatest posts by HealthStatus (see all)
Student Tips To Boost Mental Health While Studying And Taking Classes Remotely - December 7, 2020
Saving Loved Ones: 6 Ways To Help Your Loved Ones Defeat Alcohol Addiction - December 4, 2020
Staying Happy And Healthy During A Pandemic - November 30, 2020
Leave a Reply Cancel replyYour email address will not be published. Required fields are marked *
Save my name, email, and website in this browser for the next time I comment.
Sign Up For Our Newsletter
This is required.
This is required.
This is required.
